Mischief loves company.
The Little Rascals is a romance, comedy, family
film directed by Penelope Spheeris.
When nine-year-old Alfalfa falls for Darla, his
"He-Man-Woman-Hating" friends attempt to sabotage their relationship.
Alfalfa, played by Bug Hall.
Darla, played by Brittany Ashton Holmes.
Spanky, played by Travis Tedford.
Stymie, played by Kevin Jamal Woods.
Froggy, played by Jordan Warkol.
Porky, played by Zachary Mabry.
The Little Rascals is a 1994 American family comedy film produced by Amblin
Entertainment, and released by Universal Pictures on August 5, 1994.
The film is an adaptation of Hal Roach's Our Gang, a series of short films of the 1920s, 1930s, and 1940s (many of which were
broadcast on television as The Little Rascals) which centered on the adventures of a group of neighborhood children.
Directed by Penelope Spheeris, who co-wrote the screenplay with Paul Guay and Stephen Mazur, the film presents several of the
Our Gang characters in an updated setting, featuring re-interpretations of several of the original shorts.
It is the first collaboration by Guay and Mazur, whose
subsequent comedies were Liar Liar and Heartbreakers.
A sequel, The Little Rascals Save the Day, also based on Our Gang,
was released as a direct-to-video feature in 2014.
The film explores themes of friendship, shenanigan,
group of friends, woman director.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.